I make a hundred times more money
through the thing that I'm teaching you
right now than I did with my $240,000
degree. You don't understand that this
is a possibility for you right now.
Every one of us probably likes to
monetize in some way. Whether it's
through brand deals or your own offers,
whatever it may be, we want to have that
opportunity. At the very least, we want
the opportunity to do so whether or not
we take it on. But how many of you guys
are worried about, let's say, being too
salesy? How many of you guys are too
worried about not knowing what to even
sell? You don't even know what to offer.
You don't even know how people would buy
from you. You have no idea how to price
something. You have no idea how to
package something. You have no idea how
to title something, how to name
something. You don't you have all this
imposter syndrome that's rolling through
you. And today, we're going to cover
everything that it's required to make
the right content to sell so that
selling becomes easy. And that is really
through storytelling, but a specific
type of storytelling. So, we're going to
break that all down. So, what if I told
you that there was a way to package your
knowledge as a musician? What if I told
you there was a way to package your
knowledge as a illustrator? What if I
told you there was a way to package your
information even as a stay-at-home
parent or designer and actually start
monetizing online in a way that wasn't
salesy? Would you be interested in that?
Would you be interested to know at least
the game plan for storytelling to
ultimately get there? It does not mean
that you have to even start selling now.
It is just to set you up so that you
even have the opportunity to sell. The
honest truth is that I know creators
that have millions of followers that
can't monetize at all. Then I know
creators that have 5,000 followers that
I've helped them generate $100,000.
There's different ways to sell, but
there is one main way right now in 2026
that ultimately works the best. And it's
actually taking advantage of something
you already have. You just have to learn
how to leverage it. So if you don't know
who I am, my name is June U. And I am so
passionate about this. I'm probably
going to talk your ears off for the next
several hours. I'm going to give you
everything that I possibly got. I have
no notes in front of me. I just have a
deck of slides and probably at this
point like 160 hours of preparation
because I'm trying to push the envelope
of what is possible and what would
somebody be willing to give away for
free. I am willing to give all of this
away for free cuz I desperately want to
see you win. My name is June. I've been
creating content now for the last 6 and
1/2 years. I made my fair share of
mistakes. The first two and a half years
sucked. I mean, I was posting every
single day, but I wasn't growing. And
ultimately, I didn't even want to show
up online anymore. Ultimately, I I had
to kind of re-engineer and destroy some
old habits of mine and then come back to
building a better audience. I just want
to save you all that time and energy,
right? Cuz today, I have over 5 million
followers on Instagram alone. I have
generated $10 million in the last 12
months alone. I've worked with
Instagram. I've worked with Red Bull. I
get paid to speak at events. I get to
travel around the world just because of
the thing that I have in this brain of
mine. I was just recently at Can Lion. I
was speaking at their main stage, the
same stage that Mel Robbins and Steven
Bartlett were speaking at. So that's my
reality. But ultimately, I want to give
this back to you. I want to make this
accessible to you. I think you deserve
to win. And why should this information
be gatekept? I honestly think what
happens to a lot of us is that we I'm
just going to say we here cuz I'm hoping
that you agree. I don't think we're
afraid of hard work. I don't think we
are. I don't think you are. I don't
think you're looking for a get-richqu
scheme. I don't think so. At least in my
audience, you definitely aren't. I think
what we want though is to channel our
energy in the right direction. We're not
afraid of working hard. We're afraid
that we're going to work hard and then
realize that this wasn't the right
direction to put that energy in. Like
you guys are here for the long term.
Like you just wouldn't be here if that
wasn't the case. Like that's not my
people. You're just afraid that you're
going to pour all this energy and time
into it. You're going to bury yourself
publicly and then what will happen is
that you have nothing to show for it.
You're going to give up and you're going
to be like, "Oh, here's another thing
that I thought was going to be easier,
but it wasn't actually easy." And so
it's not even as if there isn't good
information out there. It's actually a
lot of the times it's conflicting. It's
conflating. You don't know who to listen
to. You see, I am not a theorist. I am a
practitioner. I will literally teach you
everything that I know up to this point
in time to make your lives easier. So
that means I'm literally going to break
down exactly how I've made the $10
million this past year. I'm not going to
hold anything back. I'm going to show
you exactly how I package an offer, like
what that even means. An offer just
means you're selling something online,
right? And I'm going to show you how I
do it. So no holds bar. All this is
going to be headed to your direction and
ultimately you're going to win with it.
Here's what you're going to get. One is
that you're going to learn exactly what
storytelling is. Number two, you're
going to learn how to put it into
content. And number three, you're going
to see how this physically leads to a
potential asset or potential business.
And you can take it as far as you want.
So you can make 100 sales if you'd like.
You can make a thousand sales if you'd
like. You can make tens of thousands of
sales like I have. Or you could just
choose to make one sale. It's entirely
up to you. But I want to give you the
opportunity to do this. I'm about to
make a claim you might not have heard
before. Storytelling content is the best
way to sell online in 2026. It's the
best way to sell without sounding
salesy. It's the best way to sell
without turning off your audience or
being called a sellout or a course guru
or whatever you want to call it. It's
the best way to sell without losing
followers, without sacrificing growth.
Because it's the best way to sell and
grow at the exact same time. It's the
best way for your product or service to
stand out in a crowded feed. Because
there is nothing nothing more
attractive, especially in the age of AI,
than being human. And there is nothing
more human than your stories. I had deep
insecurities which I believe stemmed
[music] from having such a different
upbringing than those around me. My
family immigrated from Korea to the US
when I was 3 years old. My parents never
spoke English. My dad worked
construction 12 hours a day and my mom
worked as a nail tack. But no matter how
hard they tried, we found ourselves in
hundreds of thousands of [music] dollars
in debt. When I was just 13, my mom, who
was my best friend at the time, left
overnight to a different country
permanently, and I lost contact with her
for 10 [music] years. My parents
divorced over the phone and our
financial troubles worsened until we had
to sell our childhood home and moved
five times in just a few years [music]
into smaller and smaller homes.
Eventually, my brother and I shared a
small room and my dad slept on the
living room floor. Through it all, I I
felt this great calling to be the one to
provide for [music] my family. So, I did
everything I could. I went from troubled
student in high school to being at the
top of my class as I [music] was getting
my bachelor's and masters in biomedical
engineering simultaneously. I worked odd
jobs like being a server and tried to
find ways to earn from my family. And
then in 2020, Tik Tok [music] gave rise
to short form content. So I jumped on
that opportunity although very nervous
considering I [music] had no creative
nor business background. In fact,
biomedical engineering could not be a
more polar opposite field. [music] So
there was this constant dilemma where I
didn't feel confident posting and at the
same time passive aggressive comments
like [music] you're trying too hard or
you still doing that influencer thing
were a norm. I first started with
fashion and fitness content because I
thought they were the cool things to do.
I tried every trend, but still found
myself in the 200 [music] view jail.
However, the one thing I promised myself
was that I would show up regardless. And
after posting daily for a year, I
finally saw some traction. But I decided
I wanted to make meaningful content and
start helping [music] people. And this
is when I started to use everything I've
learned as an engineer to create a
data-driven [music] content system. This
made showing up daily easy. And
ultimately, it was that system that
brought me [music] into my first
100,000, 1 million, and 5 million
followers. I was also able to use that
system to monetize. First was My Guide
to Academic [music] Success, which
earned $100,000 for four consecutive
months. Then the Learning System book,
which landed [music] number one on
Amazon's new releases and skyrocketed
the business to over a million dollars
in just 10 months. I was still a student
throughout this entire time. And I
actually remember sitting in my
classroom when I saw that $1 million
notification. [music] And now I find so
much joy in helping other creators win.
Watching someone go from insecure to
finally finding their voice. from
doubting themselves [music] to seeing
their first million views. From working
overtime to creating a life where they
can be more present with the people they
love. Whether it's moms, working
professionals, [music]
business owners, or coaches, I truly
believe everyone has a story worth
sharing. And I have the most fun helping
[music] turn those stories into
meaningful and transformational content.
It's hard to explain, but seeing their
face light up when it finally clicks,
that feeling is [music] truly addicting.
Of course, my own journey has given me
the opportunity to build incredible
businesses and [music] work with amazing
brands, which I am forever grateful for.
But the biggest win is being able to
serve others and help them win, too. I
know how hard it is. So, if I can
alleviate any of the pain, it is [music]
my greatest honor. Because when one
person finds their voice, it doesn't
just change their life, it touches
thousands [music] of others, they will
reach with their content. And that
ripple is what makes all of this
meaningful. You deserve to win and I
would do whatever it takes to get you
there. Man, is this stuff hard. Like, it
is all so unbelievably hard. Like, I
haven't slept at all in like 3 weeks
preparing for this. I care so deeply
about this. Like, I want you to win. I
desperately want to see you win to make
sure that you don't have to go through
the same struggles that I went through.
I I can't believe how tough it was for
me the first two and a half, three
years, and I'm so proud of my younger
self to actually persevere through it.
But if I can make that journey easier
for you, I think this this is all worth
it. So, I want to talk about a little
bit of of my origin. I want to speak to
it because I'm not supposed to be here
by any stretch of the imagination. And
that is why I pushed myself as hard as I
pushed myself. I immigrated from Korea
to the US when I was just 3 years old. I
was raised by a single dad. My mom, who
was my best friend, left overnight to a
completely different country, and I lost
contact with her for 10 years. So, all I
saw was suffering. We had to move from
home to home until we were in a tiny
apartment and my brother and I were
sharing a very very very small space
between the two of us and my dad was
sleeping on the living room floor. Like
it feels like it was yesterday cuz I
recall it. Like I would come home and
that's the suffering I would see every
single day. And for me, I've always had
this great chip on my shoulder to
provide. I've always had a great chip on
my shoulder to end the generational
trauma. I've always had this great chip
on my shoulder to try and finally end
all that suffering, to finally do
something about it as my parents grew
older. Unfortunately, my grandma passed
away a month and a half ago. And and
even that like experience kind of like
really hit home at at all of this. And
and it just reminds me every single day
of why I do what I do. And ultimately,
I'm important to you because if you're
here, I would assume that you're like
me. You see, in 2020, I I had no skill.
I had no creative, no business
expertise. I never read a business book
ever before. I was a full-time
bachelor's and masters biomedical
engineering student living in the
basement of this run old down building
and living off of Chipotle and that was
my only meals and this is this is my
first set of videos. Like I used to talk
in front of the camera like this. This
was my 20th take and I still felt
incredibly awkward. I'm not sure who
needs to hear this right now, but just
hold on. I know you're broken. I know
you feel alone. I know it feels like
that the world around you is crumbling
and there's nothing you can do to
[music] save it. But I want you to know
this
that sometimes things have to fall apart
in order to make way for better things.
Cuz you see, when it feels things have
to fall apart in order to make way for
better things. No matter how awkward
this kid was in front of a camera, he
certainly had a voice to be heard. You
see, in 2020, I had a willingness to
persevere through this awkward stage
that many of you guys are still in. In
2021, I was posting, but I had no reach.
I kept losing followers. But what I did
have was the ability to study and create
systems from my engineering background.
So I used to carry around like 47
notebooks that looked just like this in
different colors. And basically what I
would do is just write down everything
from formats to messaging angles to
hooks to whatever caused me the most
amount of engagement. And I started
doubling down. And what did I double
down on? Obviously the things that were
working. And even back then storytelling
was the thing that always allowed me to
win. Even as a student, I was a broke
student. I guarantee every single one of
you who was ever a student before, which
is every single one of you, hated
school, thought it was the most boring
thing ever, and couldn't wait till you
were done. I picked up a phone, even the
most boring and mundane spots, I picked
up a phone, and you're going to tell me
like, "Oh, I can't do this as a real
estate agent. Oh, I can't do this as an
artist, a pianist, a musician. Are you
kidding me?" Like, you thought school
was significantly more boring than that,
right? I did it as a student. What you
think is boring is because it has become
routine. If it has been routine for you,
I guarantee it's relatable for somebody
else. If that means it's relatable, if
you find meaning in it, then guess what?
That's your superpower you're about to
unlock. You could reach millions of
people. And that's what I did as a
student. You see, in 2023, I started to
go deeper with my story. And that
connection with my audience started to
change. It wasn't like, "Hey, fire
emoji, good outfit, dude." It was like,
"Hey, you changed my life. This is so
meaningful to me. Thank you so much for
this reminder. You've made me feel less
alone." Then in 2024, with still no
business background, without ever having
read a business book, without ever
having watched a business YouTube video,
I actually started my very first
business. I had released a PDF. Could
you believe that that thing made me a
million dollars while I was still a
student? It did. It was called the guide
to academic success, a 63page guide. Not
because I was a good business
professional, but because I was good at
content. I was good at storytelling.
I've worked with Many Chat, Red Bull.
I've spoken on stages. And in 2025, I
started a business called Creator
College. Ever since then, I've been on a
mission, a terror, a sprint. I've been
here to try and help people like
yourselves tell their stories. How many
of you guys have a voice that you want
to have actually heard? How many of you
guys have been discounting it your
entire lives? How many of you guys have
grown familiar to that opportunity where
it's like, ah, okay, I have something I
want to do, but I'm going to put the
needs of everyone else in front of me
before I even get a chance to think
about my own needs. How many of you guys
have been constantly every single time
that you try to step up and speak aloud
your own thoughts, you've been told to
quiet down? Those are my people and
those are the stories that I want to
have be heard. But in the beginning, it
wasn't as if I was overly confident. In
the beginning, I had a lot of fears. But
interestingly, all those fears vanished
when I realized one thing. It's not
actually about being a sleazy car
salesman cuz like that's what I thought
about when I thought about selling. It
was actually about serving other people
and realizing there was no better person
to help with an experience than me
because I actually care about my work.
And secondly, I've lived my experience.
At least I can speak to that truth. So
I'm like, why not me then? Why not me?
Why not me? Why can't I do it? In the
past 12 months on that tear, I've been
able to help multiple creators change
their lives, right? Just people all
around the world like yourselves. People
that have come in, didn't know a single
thing about content. This is a
hairdresser and she was able to grow I
think she's at like hundreds of
thousands of followers now. She sold a
digital product, made more money than
she knew what to do with. Then I helped
someone with a $100,000 launch named
Arabella. Then I've helped a coach named
Danielle make $150,000 in cash in a
single month. This is coach Michael who
made a million dollars I believe in the
last year and a half, two years. Then we
got Maggie and Data who made their first
six figure years of creating content.
But I say this with the thought of you
being like, "Oh, there's no way that
that's possible." Like be skeptical.
Like challenge me. Be skeptical. It's a
good thing cuz I'm going to break your
brains. Like I'm going to I'm going to
do that. I'm going to blow your mind.
You're going to be like, "What the
heck?" Like I I didn't know it was
possible. I want you to be skeptical cuz
I know that I could deliver upon this
promise. Felicity Morgan was a
successful coach before I ever worked
with her. She was smart. She was
intelligent. And she was a pure expert.
But she had plateaued after years of
creating content at 54,000 followers.
And I told her, "You can't just keep
talking at your audience. You can't just
become an educator. You have to tell
your stories. But on the back end of a
story, you can put a call to action. You
can sell a service or you can sell an
offer. And there you go. That is how you
can actually attract new people and make
money at the same time. This is the
content we worked on together that she
had posted.
>> Elena got caught up with the wrong crowd
and ended up in trouble at school. You'd
be surprised by how I handled it. First,
I was triggered. I wanted to ground him,
rip him away from those friends, say
that you're never seeing them again, but
I didn't. Instead, I asked myself, what
haven't I taught him yet that's led to
this? The answer, he didn't know how to
tell which friendships were pulling him
out of integrity. He didn't have the
skill to choose what was good for him.
So, I stayed up late for 3 days and
created a worksheet, not to make him
feel bad, but to help him reflect on how
he was letting others.
>> Just think about what she's doing in
real time. This is now a story. All of a
sudden, it doesn't feel like you're
talking at me, talking down at me. I
don't feel like I'm talking to an
expert. I feel like I'm talking to
another mom. I feel like I'm talking to
a peer.
>> Shape who he became and why. First, he
resisted, but then one activity cracked
him open. He said, "Mom, I feel anxious
around X. I don't think he's good for
me. I don't like who I am when I'm with
them. This was the moment. Instead of
protecting him from others, I gave him
the skill to protect himself. That is
what conscious parenting is. And because
of how powerful it was for Orlando, I've
made it available for other kids, too.
Just comment worksheet and I'll send you
the link.
>> Ah, but June, this is cute. It's a cute
piece of content, but business people
would never do that. And so, when you
showed me this on Monday, then you're
telling me that it was a completely
different type of content that you were
curating from the past. This one
>> Elena got caught up with the wrong
>> and
>> I've never done this one before. Yeah.
>> Which is brilliant. And remind me just
how successful this was from, let's say,
conversion standpoint. Was it like very
successful?
>> Yeah. So I think from this including
going into other things, it would be
around $160,000.
>> 160,000 AUD. You think that storytelling
doesn't sell? You are out of your mind.
Storytelling makes a normal mom like
herself become an educator that people
care about. Let's look at another one.
If you don't believe me, I'm going to
show you a few more examples and we're
going to be breaking down exactly what
they're doing. Let's look at Erica Cruz.
So Erica Cruz, same idea. She came in
and she's like, "June, I've been
creating content. I've plateaued after a
while, but I sell high ticket offers,
June. I sell high tickets. There's no
way I can sell high ticket offers with
organic content. I can't sell coaching
this way. I can't do one on's this way.
I can't sell cohorts this way." But
she's like, "I'm going to trust you,
June, because you obviously know what
the heck you're talking about." And I
told her to make this video. In fact,
this is like my exact video that I've
made that I gave her as a template. She
utilized it. She got 187,000 views. I
want you to listen to it and think about
and think, how do I feel as a result of
this video? Am I actually losing
credibility as a business owner by
telling my story, or do I feel human to
my audience?
[music]
>> Feel the earth [singing] moving.
Hear [music] my heart burst
again [music]
for this is the end.
I drowned and dreamed this moment.
[music]
So overdo I
swept away and sto [bell]
[music]
do you think that this hurts her
credibility as a business owner? I
remember when I told Felicity to tell
her story in front of everyone she's
like I'm not doing it. and she's like,
"I don't want to do it. I don't want to
tell my story." And I was like, "All
right, cool. Stay stuck where you at.
I'm good." And then we moved on and she
did it, right? And she did. And now
she's great. She's amazing at it. They
come in because they want money. They
come in because they want to build
businesses. They want to build impact.
Storytelling is the vehicle to do it.
They realize though after telling their
story, "Holy cow, my comments change, my
engagement changed." She got 10 paid
high ticket clients off of videos like
this after not being able to sell a
single thing before. Now, let's look at
Boxy, right? Boxy, same thing where he
was actually quite burnt out. So, he was
a new dad. He's like, "I don't want to
create content. I just don't want to. I
find no joy in it." I was like, "Well,
maybe you don't find joy in it because
you're teaching the same workout and
bicep tips and the same ab routines.
Maybe we should start talking about your
story and how you got there." He did a
carousel like this, ultimately made
20,000 AUD with high ticket coaching
clients. How's that possible with
organic content? It's all through
storytelling. We're going to break down
exactly how we're doing these posts.
We're going to break down how you can do
it. I'm going to give you prompts all
the way through. I am not a theorist. I
am a practitioner. Every day I fail.
Every day I challenge myself to learn
something new. Every single day I want
to push the boundaries of what is
possible. Not because I'm afraid of
failing, but because I actually want to
learn the latest new strategy so I can
give it to you. Individuals with
audiences are disrupting every industry
as we know them. Because people buy into
people. People buy into people. People
buy into people. the food and beverage
industry right now. You would think
about New Tonic with Chris Williamson
and James Smith or Feastables with Mr.
Beast or Joy Ride with Ryan Shanahan or
Bloom by Marie Llewellyn or Beauty and
Skincare Rare Beauty by Selena Gomez or
Kylie Cosmetics of Kylie Jenner or Road
with Haley Bieber or Huda Beauty with
Huda Katan or Ali Abdal Maris Brownley,
Tim Ferris, Gary Vaynerchuk, they're all
making tens of millions of dollars.
They're making hundreds of millions of
dollars on the backs of their personal
brands. Or fitness and health. Anyone
know Kayla Nis with Sweat or Pop Flex
with Casey Hoe or We Rise by Sonata Grea
or Raw Nutrition by Chris Bumstead or
Steven Bartlett, Vivian 2, Alex Heroszi,
Humphrey Yang, every single one of them
have many businesses under their one
personal brand because personal brands
are everything right now. People buy in
to people. Now the issue though is all
of them have like hundreds of employees
doing the thing for them. You guys
don't. And it's not fair that you don't
have these resources in front of you.
So, I'm going to break it down for you
because a lot of them look at my content
for work. So, I'm going to go ahead and
ensure that all of you guys get this on
a silver platter today because
storytelling content is the best type of
content to sell with. This storytelling
content challenge and storytelling in
general is going to matter more than
ever cuz feeds are getting flooded with
AI generated generic expertled content.
People aren't short of information,
they're short on connection. People
don't buy from brands, they buy from
people they feel like they know. Stories
are what makes someone feel like they
know you before you ever pitch them
anything. Here's what actually you guys
don't get because right now most of you
are here. Anyone that is a coach or an
expert in your field, listen to me very
carefully. Listen to me very carefully.
I'm calling you out in the best
healthiest way possible. You are already
smart. You're already skilled. You're
good at what you do. You're very
successful. When you're focused on
fulfilling, you can fulfill your service
very well. You're very good at teaching.
But right now, right now, if you know
that expertise right now, if you have
that information inside of you, it's not
enough to attract the audience. It's not
enough. So, for example, you can speak
in front of 300 people in an already
filled room. You can do that and you're
very great at it. People believe that,
but how the heck are you going to fill
up that room? You're not doing it.
You're probably doing it because you're
underneath a business or something or
someone asked you to come to their
event. It's not your event. How the heck
are you get a thousand people in that
room? You have to learn social media.
You have to learn content. And content,
the best way to attract new people is by
giving them a reason to care. And that
is through storytelling. Bringing
someone into your world and helping them
actually understand who you are is how
you're never going to run out of people
to sell to. You're never going to feel
like your impact is limited. You will
always be able to earn more. You'll
always be able to grow more. You'll
always be able to serve more. That's the
gap right now. Right now. And that
storytelling is going to be filling that
gap. So right now you're doing the same
tips over and over and over again.
You're doing the same thing that every
other expert in the space is doing.
You're thinking, "Okay, this is the
thing that's going to be helping me
win." But viewers say, "I've seen this
before." Storytelling content bridges
you to this other side where viewers
actually become invested in you. You
see, storytelling doesn't sell your
product. It's the reason that people
care. It sells identification. People
say, "Ah, that's me. I see myself in
them." It sells trust. It's like, "Oh, I
feel like I know this person." It sells
belief. Oh, it's worked for them. and
they're like me, then it can work for
me. And storytelling content,
storytelling content, just one of them,
can scale all three of these impacts to
thousands of people all across the world
that you wouldn't otherwise reach. What
is your other best opportunity? You
going to use ads? Great. Are you very
rich? If not, good luck. What else are
you going to do? Word of mouth? Yeah,
always be limited to that. But content,
something that is completely free for
you. The storytelling can actually scale
that trust to thousands of people that
you couldn't otherwise reach. Once
someone feels those three things,
conversion isn't a hard sell. It's their
natural next step. A lot of you guys are
doing this type of content, okay? You're
showing the final product. You're
showing your work. [music]
But if I'm scrolling through social
media, why the heck would I care? Why is
this relevant to me? But think about the
difference. This is my student,
Michelle. Michelle was like, "Hey, I
don't know what's going on. I've been
stuck at 24,000 followers for 3 years
and every time I post a piece of content
I lose followers. I say you are the
founder. You have to start telling
stories, your own stories and get people
to actually care about your work. So she
made content like this.
>> If you start here when you're drawing
your brows in, that is the very first
mistake you're making. [music] Hi, my
name is Michelle. I am a permanent
makeup artist of 10 years and I
specialize in brows. If you [music] do
this and you don't care what I think, by
all means, keep on scrolling. Girl, you
do you. As a permanent makeup artist and
someone that [music] draws people's
brows in day in and day out, I always
make sure I never start drawing brows in
in the beginning. What I've grown to
notice when I [music] start drawing my
brows in, I tend to have the heaviest
hand and then I end up gradually getting
lighter and lighter. If you are starting
in the beginning with a heavy hand, the
darkest
>> Okay, Michelle, get to the point. It's
important because you never want the
front of your brow to be the focal
point. And if that's the darkest part,
that will be the first thing people will
notice when looking at your face. Now,
of course, I'm going to give you a
better solution. Whenever you start
drawing your brows in, you always want
to make sure you start at the bottom of
the art.
>> So, look at this. So, the problem is
that she clearly demonstrates a common
mistake that people make. She shares her
experience and the method that she used
to get a better result and the final
result is actually the same as the bad
and the good. The result, the payoff
remains the same, but now there's a
reason to care because the prom pursuit
is also there. So now people trust her
over other buticians. It's not as if
there aren't other buticians out there,
but people care about her. There's
another step that you can take the way
the Michelle has done here and it's by
actually supplementing those stories
with more personal stories but
intentionally. So all these business
owners, I get it. You're like, why the
heck would somebody care about me? Why
would It's about being smart about the
stories that you tell. So Michelle has
mostly an Asian clientele. So what is
she doing? She's trying to think about
what are some commonalities between me
and them. What are some things that I
could potentially share? But I still
want to talk about my business. I still
have to know that people are actually
coming in for my work. Let me go ahead
and show you this as well.
>> Why do we love our parents the most but
talk to them with the least patience? I
just got back from a trip to China with
my parents and aunts. [music] And it was
our very first trip internationally as a
family together. And I love them. But by
day three, [music] I was running on
fumes. They'd asked me the same
questions five times in a row. What time
are we leaving? What time are we
leaving? Michelle, what time are we
[music] leaving? They were picky about
where we ate. This one's too oily. This
place looks dirty. Every single
restaurant came with a review I didn't
ask [music] for. And I catch myself
responding short, sighing, giving them
that tone. And the tone I'd never give a
client, never even with a friend.
>> Never a tone that I would give to my
client. She's it trickling this in. You
see how smart this actually is? She's
building connection with the right
audience, right? She knows who her
target avatar is. And she then went from
24,000 followers, losing followers every
time she posted to 62,000 followers with
more clients than she knows what to do
with. this is hered
>> posting about myself. I was like, "Oh,
nobody cares. Nobody cares about what I
have to do. They just want to know my
services." Uh, as a matter of fact, it
did the opposite. I started posting
about myself. I started finding a
community that were aligned with my
values and how I grew up and and I found
people that actually cared about what I
had to say and what I was interested in.
It was insane. And as a matter of fact,
in return, my business got busier, which
is so crazy to me because I'm not even
talking about beauty sometimes. So,
yeah.
>> So, now we've seen it with a service
provider, what is good to do. Now, let's
talk about physical product. Are you Are
you a jewelry designer? Are you somebody
that sells a book? Are you somebody that
sells a haird dryer? Any physical
product sellers out there? Check this
out. I bet you know what product photo
shoots are. This is what you guys are
trying to win with.
Yes, it looks gorgeous, but it's never
going to win. You can search up jewelry
and there will have be 300 other jewelry
companies that have the exact same type
of photos as you do, probably paying the
exact same agencies. There's no problem.
There is no pursuit. There is no payoff.
It doesn't stand out in a crowded feed.
But this one, this one definitely does.
This is what she's doing with a client.
By the way,
>> this is a small earring.
And now watch the difference.
Like your face is completely different.
>> Wow.
>> Look at this part. Her face is uplifted
and this is more puffy.
>> This is not like earring scale for you.
For your face, for your face features.
>> 8.7 million views. She's not a great
editor. It's not like this is a fancy
edit. It's cuz she knows how to tell now
stories through her content. Problem,
pursuit, and payoff. And ultimately what
has turned into trust has actually
turned into multiple successful launches
as well since. So Valyria had 10
different Instagram accounts, couldn't
grow a single one before for the last 10
years. She started doing this. All of a
sudden she's starting to grow. She's
like, June, what's next? What do I do
next? And I'm like, if you really want
my opinion, I would encourage you to
tell your personal story. But we have to
be smart here. We have to start
integrating about confidence, what Julia
has made you feel like. We had to
showcase products in the actual thing,
but we have to make you the focal point.
People are going to buy into people. So,
she started making content like this.
[music]
[snorts]
>> Hold your breath and count
to 10. [music]
Feel the earth move. And then
[music]
hear my heart
again.
Oh, this [music] is the end.
>> Think about this insecurities. Why is
she talking about that? Why? Because
she's trying to get her jewelry
customers actually to think, "Oh, she's
just like me." But how has she turned
into a more confident person? Let's
watch.
[music]
>> Swept away. [music] I'm sto
we
[music]
see her jewelry.
I love it. I love it.
You see the jewelry? You see what you're
not understanding is that you're not
selling jewelry. You are selling
confidence. You're selling security.
You're selling freedom. You're selling
empowerment. And ultimately, her
content, her storytelling content has
allowed her to go from never having a
single account reach multiple thousands
of followers to having 121,000 followers
to selling out multiple launches and
having 14.5 million views on a single
post alone. This is the power of
storytelling. Coaches, coaches, hear me
out. You guys suck at this the most.
You're doing the same thing as everyone
else. You're teaching the exact same
things like everyone else. And you're
like, "How come I'm not growing? Why
would they listen to you? Why? Even if
they do follow you, there's a reason why
they're unfollowing you. It's because
you're making content that looks like
this." What is up, guys? I'm at [music]
this beautiful cable machine. I don't
know if any of you guys have seen this
before, but this is honestly my new
favorite machine for cable later. I'm
going to show you how it works. So,
[music] we've got it set up around knee
height, maybe around a little bit
underneath the hips. We don't [music]
have any attachments on, but there's
it's dual, so like we can we can pull
both of them. All of my students come in
here. The first two folks were my
student. This is another student of
mine. If you're joining the storytelling
content challenge and your content looks
like in the bad, you're about to turn
into the good. And this is the stuff
that we teach. Check this out. Think
about the storytelling that has evolved
here and why somebody would actually
care. Think about the problem, pursuit,
and payoff.
>> My chest is by far my biggest
insecurity. [music] You see, 4 years
ago, the only reason I started going to
the gym was because I was super insecure
of [music] my sunken chest. And
honestly, I thought that doing a lot of
bench press was going to fix that. But
the truth is, I trained chest for years
before they started to actually grow.
So, if your chest is something that you
want to change, too, here are three.
Right? Even even if I don't play the
whole thing, it's like 100 times more
engaging. Right? Even if I don't even
finish the video, you're like, "Oh, I
actually have a reason to care." This is
the difference between a coach that
makes $10,000$12,000 and a coach that's
continuously able to scale because
you're going to continuously grow their
audience. If you're a coach that feels
salesy, like you're losing followers,
that you're stuck at a few thousand
followers, you have to try storytelling
content. You see, he has done this. And
what did he do? He actually supplemented
it with now a different type of
story-led content, origin content,
content that actually showcases why
you've started the business in the first
place. This is what founderled
storytelling content looks like that
you're going to learn within the
storytelling content challenge, too.
>> Two months ago, I dropped out of my
final year of law school to become a
glorified unemployed gym bro. Okay, not
entirely true, but let me explain. See,
growing up, I was the jack of all trades
kid. Pretty good at most things,
excellent at none. I did well in school,
played every single sport, even dabbled
in music, drama, public speaking, hell,
even magic. But nothing ever clicked. No
spark, no passion. And like every other
regular kid, I thought the goal was
simple. finish uni, make my parents
proud, get a stable job. But somewhere
along the way, I found fitness. What
started as gym [music] clips and thirst
traps turned into something real. And
and what you think right now is like,
oh, a guy that's so good at editing, a
guy that of course has the charm and
charisma to do it, had the exact same
fears as you. He was insecure as much as
you are, right? He was thinking about,
there's no way I could do this. There's
no way I could do this on my phone. Why
would anyone care about my story as a
trainer? Guess what? He started doing
that. He grew his audience 25,000 more
followers and grew his high ticket
coaching program too. People do not buy
your product first. Listen to me very
carefully. People buy into people. They
buy into you first. Every story that
sells has the exact same shape. What
problem? Pursuit payoff is the way that
you actually make storytelling content
that sells. I'm just going to teach you
now why that actually is the case. You
see, the part that you're missing right
now is the pursuit isn't just your
method. It doesn't make for just a good
story. It actually becomes your offer.
It becomes your intellectual property.
It is thing that you package and sell in
a challenge. The way that I'm selling in
a challenge, the way that you could sell
in any type of physical product, in any
way that you can sell a service, you can
actually sell with your pursuit. The
pursuit is the method. And I'm going to
break down exactly what that means. Any
trainers in here? Just an example for
you. Maybe a problem that you have
actually come across is that you
couldn't stick to a routine. So, you
actually decided to make it easier for
you and you did a home workout system
that worked for you. Then great. Then
you're going to show the payoff and
maybe you started seeing huge
improvements in your training. Then you
can actually package the pursuit into a
30-day at home workout program. What?
How's that possible? Well, the problem
makes it relevant to somebody. Somebody
sees themselves in you. Then they see
your method and they actually see that
it works for them. Of course, they're
going to want to know more. This is how
you can sell something. How about a
wedding photographer? While the problem
might be that you're spending 40 plus
hours editing every wedding and you were
burning out, the pursuit is that you
built a streamlined editing workflow
plus client communication templates and
the payoff is that you saved 70% of your
time. What you can sell something called
shoot and scale. This could be a course
that you sell to other photographers.
The pursuit is the offer. The pursuit is
your method that people have already
bought into. You just now have to put a
call to action to your contact. Maybe a
skincare brand owner. The problem could
be you struggled with acne and you
couldn't find any products that work.
Your pursuit is that you started
handmixing your own treatments using
specific ingredient ratios. The payoff
is that you cleared up your acne and now
you have glowing skin. Wo, you now have
your own signature skinincare product.
This is how every one of those hundred
million dollar companies have started.
This is how my challenge in 48 hours
from a weight list an email made a
million dollars. It's through
storytelling. That method becomes your
intellectual property. The thing that
you package and offer. Your problem made
somebody care. Your payoff showed that
it would work for them. The pursuit is
now the method you sell. That is the
point of the problem pursuit payoff.
It's not just an engaging story. It is
literally how you sell. And that is why
the three piece are so important that
you actually learn. Now, I'm going to
show you this physically with my
storytelling content challenge. The
storytelling content challenge literally
how it made a million dollars in 48
hours has been done through the thing
that I'm literally telling you right
now. 12 months ago, I had no idea what
the heck a storytelling content
challenge would have been. I have no
idea. I had I had no thought of that in
my brain. I didn't start there at all. I
didn't think like, oh, I'm going to be a
successful business owner, make a
million dollars in 48 hours. I didn't
think of it like that. I thought of my
problem, though. I was like, shoot, I
need to grow more. I need to grow an
audience so that people care. And so, I
started telling my story. The pursuit
was I literally started sharing my story
online. And naturally, I started coming
up with ways that I was doing it, right?
So, the three Ps, the storytelling
wheel, I'll be fully honest, they didn't
even have names yet. Like, it was just
how I was doing it. But naturally, the
payoff is that it was successful, right?
I actually like the stories that I told.
And if you ever join my storytelling
content challenge, you're going to learn
how to tell stories in a way that feels
aligned to you, that you're going to
feel very confident about. So, the
payoff then is like making other people
say, "Holy cow, June, this is like
really good." And I'm like what you like
you that was just for me. So I started
thinking I'm like okay so if other
people are wanting this huh and they're
asking me now questions about how to
effectively do it. Ah there is something
I could actually start labeling these
into frameworks packaging them as my own
IP and start developing videos and
content around storytelling. And you've
probably seen this piece of content. You
may have seen my stories up to this
point in time. Then I actually teach
these frameworks to my team because they
had no idea what those were. That's the
storytelling framework. My first
product, the guide to academic success,
the one that I told you I made a million
dollars with while being a student, did
the exact same thing. What did I do?
Problem? I started showing content about
the fact that I sucked at studying.
Pursuit. I started talking about how I
was getting better at studying with
evidence-based learning strategies. The
payoff was that I actually graduated.
The pursuit is the thing that I packaged
into calling the guide to academic
success. A PDF. A PDF made a million
dollars. A PDF. I was able to use that
money to actually pay off my dad's
$225,000 of lifetime debt. And I also
paid off my entire student loan debt.
How about this? Let's look at creator
college, right? How to create a college
even ignite into something like it is
today. Problem. I wanted to grow on
social media. I was able to do so. And
guess what I did? I started to actually
talk about, oh, it was this method. It
was this framework and I did it and
people cared about it. Then the payoff,
it was serious growth and success. And
people started asking how. Then created
college became this thing that now I'm
actually like look at this. You are not
a fitness creator. You are not a travel
creator. You're not a fashion creator.
You're not a beauty creator. You're not
a tech creator. You're not a food
creator. You, my friends, are the niche.
I truly believe you do not need a niche.
I truly believe
you are the niche. Now, we've done this
in New York, and I hope that you guys
can beat the New York room. There's a
thousand more of you. I'm going to ask
if you guys
>> This is actually unbelievable. This was
like a dream come true for me. And I had
the entire room say something. Look how
loud this actually sounds. It's
unbelievable.
>> I am the niche. Those four words at the
top of your lungs. Three,
two, one.
>> How cool is that? But it's the impact,
guys. Like, I have now been able to take
care of my dad. You know how the most
successful, the moment that I get chills
with every single time is not the moment
that I bought a car. I still drive the
same 2015 Jeep. I'm not someone that has
a fancy life. This this watch that I
have on my wrist was a graduation gift
to my brother that was like 145 bucks.
These things don't give me much meaning,
but what gives me meaning was the
ability to slide over $300,000 of a
check written to my dad over dinner and
seeing him cry and having him fall into
my arms and having that moment with him
has been everything. You know, the
amount of suffering I had seen, I had
seen things that I would never wish on
my worst enemy. The things that I had to
see, the depression, the mental health,
the things that everyone was going
through in my family. And at my age, as
the youngest kid, seeing all of that
destroy everyone within my family and
having to know this and say, "No, it's
going to be on me." Like, I'm going to
do something about it. I'm going to do
why? No one's coming to save us. It is
on me. So, guess what? I did it. And now
today, through storytelling, I get a
chance to give back to even people that
I couldn't have ever met before. I'm
giving back to you right now. This is
serious stuff. This is intimate stuff.
This is things that so personal to our
own respective goals. And I could not
have ever ever dreamt of this moment.
And that's why I'm so impassioned to be
in front of you today and make sure that
you guys become storytellers yourselves.
Every single time any product that I've
ever sold, the problem got attention.
The payoff showed how it worked. And it
was the pursuit people actually paid
for. This pursuit becomes that offer.
And you start to recognize, holy cow,
people actually even want to buy from
you before you even had a product yet.
Check this out. If you don't have a
product yet, build an audience, tell
your story, and people start championing
you. If you don't have a product yet, I
know I talked about service owners,
physical product sellers, coaches,
trainers, but if you don't have a
product yet, this is perfectly for you.
The storytelling content challenge is
perfectly for you because you're going
to build an audience the right way. If
people champion you, you can sell
whatever you want and people will buy
into that. Let me explain right now. You
can just start with your life. You can
start about work. You can start about
relationships. You can talk about
interests, experiences, learnings,
whatever it is that you want. Do the
three Ps. Three Ps in every single one
of your posts. You will grow 10,000
followers. But I'm not going to force
you to talk about specific topics.
Actually want to explore with your life.
If you don't have a product yet, work,
relationships, interests, experiences,
and learnings. But guess what happens
naturally? One of those things are going
to really land. Your audience will love
it, and you're going to love it. And
that pursuit becomes your offer. You're
actually naturally falling into a
product while not sacrificing growth
without overthinking like oh I need a
product before I start oh I need to I
need to have this perfect no you just
start by telling your story and
naturally people gravitate towards
things and that's the thing that you're
going to ultimately sell that step four
becomes an offer like you can make a lot
of money through storytelling and that
pursuit turns into a method and I want
to be crystal clear it's not like right
now you're going to be able to be like
oh this is a thing in my life that's
going to make a lot of money that's not
how it works everything that you live
feels boring to to you because you're
just like, "Oh, I just done that. Like,
I didn't even think about it. It's just
how I operate it." In hindsight, like I
am doing right now with the storytelling
content challenge. I had no idea that
that would be interesting. And you're
like, "But dude, of course you did.
Like, you've done this before. Like,
storytelling of course would be
attractive." I had no idea. You know how
many other people, by the way, have
tried to sell storytelling things that
haven't worked? It's because of the
content. It's because the audience, the
the way that I've been able to make
people champion this product launch. In
hindsight, it actually looks like a
method. So, what I want you to think
about is the following. Ask yourself
these three questions. What did I do
repeatedly that I stopped noticing as a
thing? Here are three prompts. Think
about the stuff that feels too obvious
or too small to mention. For me, the
problem pursuit payoff is like so
obvious because I've been doing it for 6
years. I don't even think about it.
Naturally, I'm like, "Oh, wait. People
don't realize it's a real thing." The
pursuit is often being hidden in the
boring repeated things that you're
doing. I didn't think testing
evidence-based learning strategies was a
product. It was just literally what I
did every day. Number two, ask yourself
this. What would I tell a friend to do
step by step if they had my exact
problem? If I was just in a room, don't
think about making money. Don't think
about a dollar association. If a friend
came to you on a FaceTime call or in
person, how would you help them? If you
could answer this in more than one
sentence, like it's not something super
easy. If you could actually explain a
process, ah, you have a pursuit there
that you can sell. Vague answers sound
like advice. Just be consistent. But
specific answers sound like a method.
Like, I posted for this long this way.
So, guess what? A 21-day content
challenge is a method for 21 days. I'm
breaking it back week by week. There's a
reason why the challenge is instructed
that way and it's going to break your
brains. The third prompt that you can
ask yourself is what did I get wrong
first, but before I actually got it
right. So, what are the common mistakes
that I made that I didn't even think
were mistakes that I could package? Oh
my gosh, those are problems. Now, I
could actually put that in the first P
of the problem pursuit payoff. Oh my
gosh, I actually can tell like 45
stories cuz I had like 45 different
mistakes. Here's the best way of putting
it. Every person right now that is
making the most amount of money online
are not the biggest experts. They're not
the smartest people online. They're not
the best expertise. They're not. They're
people that know how to tell good
stories. They're the ones that feel
really human. They're the 35-year-old
other moms. They're like the 47year-old
teachers. They're like the 53y old
people that have lived experience.
They're the 70 years old people that
never actually touched content before.
Why are they making millions of dollars?
And these people that have trained for
this, that have been studying for 55
years for this, why are they not making
a single dime? It's because it's not
enough to be smart. It's more important
to be human. How else are you going to
do it? Like, what is your other option?
Be a failure forever. Like, what what
like what how other way could you
actually get in front of people? Pay for
ads? Like, how? Like, think about what
is here. I'll show you. I'll show you
right now. Travis is in the storytelling
content challenge. And I've worked with
him before. You might know who Travis is
because he's now like a very very very
very big deal. This guy Travis 912,000
followers the guy that sells music that
goes on tours that sells out festivals
that is with one of the most popular DJs
right now. This guy Travis, guess what?
He does my program. He's doing the
story. You know this guy, the guy that
you think, oh, as a musician there's no
way I could sell. How else are you going
to sell? There's no other way to sell.
Oh, why is he talking about things about
what he's learning? Why is he talking
about sobriety? Why is he talking about
sobriety? He's a musician. You shouldn't
be talking about Sabbri. Why is he doing
this? Ah, why does he have 912,000
followers for the exact same reason?
It's storytelling. Let's look at
something completely different. You're
like, there's no way. It only works for
There's no way. I I I'm just can't do
it. I'm not I'm not cool enough. Let's
look at Terrence. Terrence is a music
production coach. You know, he was
posting for a long time and had hadn't
grown a single person in his audience.
Look what he does. I want to just even
I'll just show you his content right
from the get-go. Let's look at it. Okay,
let's look at what he does for his
content. Oh, okay. Hi, I'm Terrence. I
help produce. Okay, I'm a producer,
songwriter, and artist. Here's my sto
Oh, story. He told a story. No way. Not
as a music producer. Oh, wait. Why is he
talking about his marriage? That's
weird. As a musician, why is he talking
about Why is he showing his younger
self? Why is he talking about Oh. Oh.
Why is he talking about year 2016? Why
is he Oh, I get it. Both of them are
making a lot of money doing music. A lot
of them are doing stuff that you could
have never imagined because they're
doing it through storytelling. I spent
$200,000 I spent $242,000
on my college education. $242,000 on my
college education. And not a single one
of you guys would have blinked if I told
you I spent $242,000 on biomedical
engineering degrees. I make a hundred
times more money through the thing that
I'm teaching you right now than I did
with my $240,000 degree. And no one
blinked an eye on that. The reason why
you're blinking an eye on this is
because you don't get it. Like you don't
understand that this is a possibility
for you right now. I am about to show
you something called
angles. And I don't mean like how good
you can look on camera like those
angles. I'm talking about how can you
actually give new life to the same story
over and over and over again. So how is
this possible? Let me explain.
Let's say you're starting a new hobby.
It's like but Julian, I can't talk about
the same hobby like 12 times. I I'm
going to show the most boring thing that
you can possibly think of. And I want to
show you how you can turn this into
multiple different stories. There's some
questions that you can ask yourself. You
can ask yourself questions like this.
You're starting to be introduced to
phase one of angles. How can you turn
one story into multiple pieces of
content? You introduce it into different
ways. Let me explain. So, if we think
about mentally, how can how can starting
a new hobby be an interesting story?
Let's think.
You know the whole like left brain,
right brain thing. Maybe it's helping
you train a new part of your brain.
Let's talk about spiritually. How is
starting a new hobby helping you
spiritually.
Then we have physically.
Okay. So I am trying to break down to
you how one event can actually turn into
multiple stories. And there's another
now permutation that adds to this. Each
one of these will actually have its own.
What? You're telling me that this one
moment can have its own respective
physical problem pursuit payoff? Of
course it can.
Pursuit. I don't know what a hobby is,
but I'm thinking about like I've decided
to join the wreck league softball. I
don't know if that's only a US thing,
but you get the point. Then payoff being
like
cool. I used to be at my desk all the
time and as I get older, I'm feeling
more stiff. Pursuit. I've decided to
join the Wreck League softball thing. So
that's the pursuit payoff is I now feel
like I have something to show up for and
do physically. Great. Whoa. You have one
story. [gasps] But you're telling me
that every single one of these actually
have each problem pursuits and payoff.
Yes, I am. Jessica, so let's say
spiritually um problem is I feel unal
alive. I feel bored. I feel like life
sucks. Pursuit is I am finally going to
put my own joy and adventure first. I
don't know what's another hobby. I
decided to pick up on cloud watching. Is
that is that a hobby? Payoff is I like
clouds and I find that my younger self
who used to stare into the sky with
dreams has something to look forward to.
All of a sudden, one event can have 1 2
4 5 6 7 8 9 12 acts. And every single
one of these can actually be own
problems. This payoff can actually turn
into a problem. Maybe the problem here
is I actually got injured. Pursuit is
and the payoff could be
maybe the payoff is sad this time. And
you say, I feel like I'm restarting
again. That could be a payoff. So you're
telling me that if we zoom out, we're
going to have one another another story,
another story, another story. And you're
like, June, how are you so brilliant?
How are you doing this? This isn't
something that I've invented. You, my
friends, have always have always have
always have always always had a story.
You just never knew how to have the eye
for it. You're going to realize now that
you have an eye for it, which means this
stores into your memory. You make better
content. And this, my friends, is a
cycle. The reason why I can do this
whole thing and say that you have
endless stories around you is because
our human brains work that way. So, if
you think about eyes, how do you have an
eye for something? There's something
called the red car theory. If you ever
bought a red car, you're going to go and
look at the street and realize there's
so many red cars on the streets. It's
not because all of a sudden Toyota
started selling more red cars. It's
because you have relevance. You built an
eye for it. This is the real thing that
I'm trying to teach you. Having an eye
for the things around you. And that's a
skill that's going to make you a better
speaker. Do you suck at making friends?
It's going to get you new friends. Do
you suck at uh presentations at work?
It's going to make you a better
presenter because you don't realize, but
storytelling is a skill that goes beyond
just content alone. I am training the
skill for it, but I have to package this
from a content perspective because then
you'll understand it. Albert Einstein
has said this quote that the definition
of insanity is doing the same thing over
and over again and expecting a different
result. How long is it going to take you
to realize that you've been insane this
whole time? You're 44 years old. You're
44. When is when are you going to wake
up to the reality that you have never
put yourself first? When are you going
to wake up to the reality that maybe you
don't like the job that you have? When
are you going to wake up to the reality
that you lost your spark a long time
ago? It's not because you don't have it
in you. It's because it's been hidden.
It's because somewhere along the way,
someone has told you to stop talking
when you had an idea. It's because
someone along the way has told you that
you weren't good enough. Maybe it was an
ex that broke up with you and cheated on
you for some other reason, was flirting
with you, someone else person. It broke
your heart. Maybe it was a bully. Maybe
it was a teacher that you hated. Maybe
it was that bus driver that was weirdly
mean to you. But maybe it was that
friend that actually didn't turn out to
be a friend and backstabbed you.
Something somewhere along the way,
you've allowed someone else's
interpretation of your story run your
own. You've allowed someone else's voice
actually turn into your own. The person
that has told you that you weren't good
enough, somehow it's gone into your
brain and out of your own lips. And all
of a sudden, that has become your
reality. Way you could wake up to the
reality that you have been insane this
whole time. Not because you don't have
it in you, but because you've allowed
other people to run that story. Tell it
yourself. Find power in it. Tell it. Own
it. Look at this. Dr. Prime, one of the
most popular quotes of all time. The
most common regret that people have on
their deathbed is that they lived their
life according to the desires of others,
not how they wanted to. You really think
that when you're on your deathbed,
you're going to regret posting content
and trying to show up for your own
dreams? You really think that that's the
thing that you're going to regret? Or do
you think that you're going to regret
never trying in the first place? You
know, the reason why I feel so
impassioned to talk about this is now
that I've quote unquote made it, I'll be
fully honest with you, all the people at
this level suck. They suck. A lot of
them have no idea what they're talking
about. You know, a lot of the times I'm
on these podcasts and now that I have a
podcast, we bring on guests and I'm
like, they have no idea what they're
talking about. They suck. These people
that you look up to, these people that
are having these successes, you look at
them, you're like, there's no way I
could achieve it. If I could show you
how they were in real life, you would
say, "If they can do it, I can too. I
guarantee it." You see, the thing that
you're going to regret is that when you
grow older, you're going to realize
every outcome is the same for all of us.
We're gone. And that's when everything's
going to hit you. It will. You're gonna
be like, "I let Sally and Joe or I let
my dad or I let my cousin or my teacher
or I let my manager dictate exactly how
I felt about myself dictate everything
that I did for my life." That's what
you're going to actually require. The
average age of a millionaire in the US,
which is earlier than most, is 61 years
old. You're looking at these
19-year-old, 18-year-old successful
millionaires, and you're like, I can't
do this internet thing. It's not too
late. It's never too late. The only time
you can ever lose in life is if you give
up. Is it okay if I'm honest with you in
this moment? You know, I'm telling you
to talk about your stories. I might as
well tell you mine. I can't tell you the
amount of moments that I've wanted to
quit. I can't describe it to you in
words. Like, if you saw the things that
I saw growing up, there's no way. You
know, I remember when I was about a year
and a half into college and I was never
naturally smart. I was biomedical
engineering student and basically I was
having a really rough time in school. My
dad got sick and so of course because he
doesn't speak English, I went back home
and I took him to the hospital and all
things there were fine. But I was laying
there in my childhood bed looking at me
in this mirror that I have and I was
like, "Holy cow, I'm a loser." Like, I
have nothing to show for the work that
I've poured into this. I've worked so
hard since I was 16 years old. I didn't
go to parties. I didn't drink. I didn't
hook up with people. I didn't I didn't
do any of that stuff. And I was like,
I've been doing this for 8 to nine
years. Every one of my friends in high
school was like, "This kid is a loser."
Friday nights Friday nights while
everyone else was going out, I was going
to the gym. I was trying to take care of
myself cuz I knew that I had to do
things to actually get ahead in life.
And still nine years later, I found
myself in that bedroom. I'm like, man,
maybe they were right. Maybe they were
right. I looked at it and I was like,
"My dad's still struggling. I still
don't have a relationship with my mom.
It's not like my siblings are going to
help us get out of this. Man, maybe they
were right." Interestingly enough, so
basically I lived in a basement and my
dad was waking up. He always wakes up at
like 3:30 a.m. to go to work. And he had
actually at that moment in time, he was
making a cup of coffee like he always
does for me before he goes to work. and
he would drop off that cup of coffee.
But interestingly, that day he actually
dropped it and he didn't crash. It was
one of those mugs, just made a loud
noise and it like weirdly woke me up in
that moment. All of a sudden, I I
stopped getting into my own lost thread
of thoughts and that thing broke me out
of it for a second and reminded me of
why I do what I do. You see, the amount
of respect that I have for every single
one of you, it's not because you're
already successful. It's that you're
willing to work hard even in the midst
of the struggle. Anyone can work hard
when they're winning. it is the time in
which they're not winning that
[clears throat] I have so much respect
for you. And so when it broke me out of
that reality, I was like, who the heck
am I to believe in someone else's lie
about me? I should continue doing what I
do. In that moment, about 3 and 1/2
weeks later, I started making content
that actually grew for the first time.
About 6 and 1/2 months later, I actually
started to do well in school. About a
year and a half later, I got my first
internship called West Pharmaceutical
Services. For someone that was
struggling with their academics, that
was probably a big leap. Then I think
about the next experience. Then I got
one at Glasco Smith Klein, one of the
top 10 pharmaceutical companies in the
world. I started to do better in school.
I started making better content. But the
honest truth is that it still wasn't the
made it moment that you think it was. It
wasn't. Every single day, I still had
the insecurity. I still had the doubts.
I thought that maybe people were right.
But the one thing that I wasn't willing
to let go of is to tell my story.
Because the honest truth is that I
didn't want to be on my deathbed and
wondering if I could if I could have
made it. You see, our greatest fear is
not that we're inadequate. my greatest
fears that were powerful beyond measure.
In that moment, I knew that I was
powerful. I just didn't know if I wanted
to try harder. I didn't know if I wanted
to try harder because if I failed, then
I would be faced with all the realities
that I wasn't good enough. But the one
thing that for some reason I couldn't
let go of was to share my story. You
fast forward another year or so and my
audience is growing. I'm getting nearer
to graduating and still there isn't
nothing to show for it. It's not like I
have more money in the bank account,
better grades, so it doesn't show
anything in terms of my career. But
something that I built over that long
period of time without winning for about
14 years was this idea that you will
work hard no matter what it is. And it
shows you a completely different level
of resilience. It does. And it's like
I'm going to [clears throat] win. Like I
will. The only way that I can lose is if
I quit. Then you fast forward and about
the last year before I graduate I had a
5-year program. In that fifth year I
grew to a million followers. In that
same year I actually got that internship
with Novartis and started a digital
microscope. I built a digital atomic
microscope while also starting my first
business. And that's the business that
did a million dollars while I was still
there. That's what everyone thinks is an
overnight success. You have to be insane
to put the amount of work that I do. You
have to be insane. What other person
What other person I've made my millions
of dollars. Money is obviously not the
thing that's driving me. Obviously, what
other 25year-old kid would make multiple
millions of dollars and say, "I'm not
near done yet." Who would Who else would
do this? Who else would do this? I went
from a 30-hour live master class.
Immediately the next day, I flew to Can
to speak at Can Line. It was for 4 days.
Immediately after that, barely any sleep
while still preparing while we're going
through it. I went straight to London.
From that, I hosted the London event.
The first day that I was there,
everything went wrong. We had to fix it.
We had to put out fires. The next day
that I was there, we were hosting an
event for 1,300 people. The next day, I
hosted a live inerson mastermind. Did it
for two days in a row, a full day. Then
immediately what I do after that I did
three days of podcasts where I had to do
all the research for them, prep for
them, set up the studios for them. I did
that barely any sleep for that entire 3
and a half week period. Then I went to
France and that's where the storytelling
content challenge happened. From the
storytelling content challenge, I felt a
light in my soul that I haven't felt in
a long period of time because everything
feels so aligned to me in this moment.
Everything that I suffered with that
moment in time where I heard that jug of
my dad's coffee dropping onto the
ground, it's like every little bit of
that fear and struggle and exhaustion
has come to this moment in time where
I'm like, "Yeah, yeah, this is it. This
is it." If I can find the way to
actually serve you and have you find
your voice. This is story time. If I can
help somebody feel more confident, more
secure in their experience, then man,
was this worth it. Storytelling is in
all of us. And if I can somehow make you
feel and believe in that, then I think
that I'm doing my job.
>> Of course, I love you.
>> You have no idea how terrified I am in
this moment. You have no idea. Right
here, I'm like shaking. I want you to
feel this.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Midas
[laughter]
[snorts]
6 months ago, my grandma passed away
unexpectedly. 8 months before she
passed, dementia was quickly erasing her
memories. But one question always
remained, and it might be a very Korean
thing to do, a very Korean grandma thing
to do. How's your work going?
For 40 years, she gave her whole life to
being a nurse in the ER. And it's why I
actually studied biomedical engineering
in the first place. By the way, I had no
business studying. That is way out of my
league. And I did it. So, how the heck
am I going to tell the person that
inspired [snorts] me to do all of this
while she's going through what she's
going through, that I'd quit and started
making videos instead. Probably not a
very good thing to tell a Korean
grandma, especially at her age. So, I
smiled and I said, "Hey, it's going
great, Grandma. It's going all right."
Three months before she passed, there's
one video, especially of me in New York
City. We were hosting our event and she
saw a video of me like this, like this.
And she was like, "Oh, my grandson." She
didn't care about what I did for work
the whole time. It's the only things
that she could remember. But in that
moment, she was proud in that moment. In
that moment, she was proud. She's proud
of my heart. She never cared about a
title. She only cared about God's
calling for me. And she believed, even
at her age, it was for me to help people
tell their stories. She knew I had a
gift. She's like, "He's going to do
something about it." In February, I got
a phone call at 3:00 a.m. telling me
that she was gone. By the way, this is
probably the worst time, if there's ever
a good time to have a family's death.
But we were right before preparing for
an event. It's like 3 and 1/2 days
before. I got a phone call at 3:00 a.m.
So, what did I do? Of course, I
immediately flew out to Philadelphia the
next day. I took care of the things I
need to take care of. I paid for all the
things I need to pay for to make sure
that at least we could honor her when we
did. By the way, that two days later, I
still carried on with the event. Then I
flew out, did the whole things that I
was supposed to do. You see, she spent
her whole life advocating for people,
and I feel as though I'm carrying her
legacy forward. 6 months later, I went
on a terror. I've been on that terror.
I'm writing the coattales of it, and I
still feel like I got a lot of it left.
I'm on a mission to help as many people
as possible tear their stories, big or
small. I think I have somehow built this
gift of mine, which feels like a mirror.
I don't think that I'm uber talented,
but I think I am really good at
reflecting who you are. In a way that
feels kind, but in a way that stings a
little bit, just enough to keep you
coming back for more. You see, for some
odd reason, I could be in the UK, barely
have an audience, sold out. They all
come again, I don't think it has
anything to do with me. Look at them. Do
you see a single person that's looking
away? Every single person is looking. I
think it's just because I'm really good
at reflecting the opportunity. I think
I'm really good at reflecting the lie
that you've been telling yourself over
and over again that you don't have a
story. I'm going to end with one final
message. I believe in you. And I want
you to share that belief even if you
can't hold it for yourself. Just take my
belief in you because again, I am so
sorry that someone along the way or
something has told you that you weren't
good enough, that you couldn't do it.
I'm so sorry, even more so that you've
believed in it. Our greatest fears are
not that we're inadequate. Our greatest
fears are that we're powerful beyond
measure. We're not afraid that we don't
have the potential. We're afraid to act
on it and fail and to be faced with the
reality that we might not be as good as
we think we are. You have a decision to
make because that feeling isn't going to
go away. With that being said, I love
you guys so much. Thank you guys and
I'll see you